<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MSDTTeachingApp</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="city_name">Yangon</string>
    <string name="exampleParagraph">Yangon (formerly known as Rangoon) is the largest city in Myanmar (formerly Burma). A mix of British colonial architecture, modern high-rises and gilded Buddhist pagodas define its skyline. Its famed Shwedagon Paya, a huge, shimmering pagoda complex, draws thousands of pilgrims annually. The city\'s other notable religious sites include the Botataung and Sule pagodas, both housing Buddhist relics.The city site is a low ridge surrounded by delta alluvium. The original settlements were located on the ridge, but the modern town was built on alluvium. Subsequent expansion has taken place both on the ridge and on delta land. The local climate is warm and humid, with much rainfall.
        The centre of the city, called the Cantonment, was planned by the British in 1852 and is laid out on a system of blocks, each 800 by 860 feet (245 by 262 metres), intersected regularly by streets running north–south and east–west. As Yangon’s population increased in the 20th century, new settlements were built in the north, east, and west that greatly expanded the city’s area.The most notable building in Yangon is the Shwe Dagon Pagoda, a great Buddhist temple complex that crowns a hill about one mile north of the Cantonment. The pagoda itself is a solid brick stupa (Buddhist reliquary) that is completely covered with gold. It rises 326 feet (99 metres) on a hill 168 feet (51 metres) above the city. Yangon is the site of several other major religious edifices, including the World Peace Pagoda (1952) and the Sule and Botataung pagodas.
</string>
    <string name="camera">Camera</string>
    <string name="setting">Setting</string>
    <string name="btnUpload">Upload</string>
    <string name="btnDiscard">Discard</string>
    <string name="forgotPW">Forgot Password?</string>
    <string name="login_header_text"><b>Welcome</b> Please login here</string>
    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="menu_tools">Tools</string>
    <string name="menu_share">Share</string>
    <string name="menu_send">Send</string>
    <string name="title_activity_code_lab">CodeLabActivity</string>
</resources>
